reversephonelookup2.com 2016-03-03

# Privacy Policy

reversephonelookup2, Inc. provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of the reversephonelookup2.com website located at http://reversephonelookup2.com (website) and any services or software offered by reversephonelookup2.com. This Privacy Policy applies only to information provided to us by users through reversephonelookup2.com

## Information - What We Collect and How We Use It

### What we collect

When you submit information for publication on our Website, all information supplied will be available to the public. Please exercise caution when supplying personally identifying information. Avoid posting your email address and phone number within the post message.

In the course of using reversephonelookup2.com, some of what we will ask you for is considered "Personal Information". This term refers to personally identifiable information about you that can be used to contact or identify you. Such Personal Information typically includes but is not limited to your name, phone number, email address, credit card or other billing information, and home and business postal addresses.

We may also ask for other information, such as your zip code and personal preferences, which is typically considered "Non-Identifying Information" since it can't be used to identify you on its own. Sometimes Non-Identifying Information can be considered part of your Personal Information if it is combined in such a way that it enables you to be identified (for example, combining your zip code with your street address).

Like most other Internet sites, we use cookies to personalize and enhance your experience on our sites. No personal information is gathered via the cookies.

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, you should note that cookies are necessary to provide you with certain website features.

### Links to third party Web sites

Our sites offer hyperlinks to other Web sites which may have information policies and practices different from ours. We do not control and are not responsible for the privacy policies, practices, or the content of any third party Web sites. Once you've left our Web sites via such a link or by clicking on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine how they will handle any information they collect from you.

### Third party advertising

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our Web sites. These companies may use cookies, pixel tags, or otherwise independently collect non-personally identifiable information from you and use this information about your visits to this and other sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. We do not control their collection and use of information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

### Security

reversephonelookup2.com is very concerned with safeguarding your information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access.

### Phishing

reversephonelookup2.com is concerned about identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing". We treat safeguarding your Personal Information as a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your account ID, login password, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited email or telephone communication. For more information about phishing, visit the Federal Trade Commission's website.

### Privacy Policy Changes

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time. Any modifications to our Privacy Policy will be reflected on this page.

### Questions and comments

Questions regarding this privacy statement should be submitted via the feedback form.
